## **ALISON HALL**

# 07787 814689 alison adrian hall@hotmail.com

#### **Profile**

An experienced IT Operations and Application Support Analyst at home in 24x7 high-pressure environments from global financial companies to local support teams. Committed to delivering a quality end-to-end service and meeting service level agreements and key performance indicators.

## **Employment History**

## Remote Operations Analyst Tier 3

February 2019 – present

**Inspired Gaming** 

The Maltings, Wetmore Road, Burton-on-Trent. DE14 1SE

## Responsibilities include:

- Provide L3 Application Support across a variety of products and platforms, including multi-function gaming terminals and mobile gaming applications.
- Scripting updates in Oracle SQL to correct data, as well as performing queries to provide information and reporting for other teams.
- > Liaising with developers and other technical staff to ensure timely fault resolution.
- > Pro-active management of issues and alerting.
- > Creating and maintaining support documentation.

### **Operations Analyst**

July 2016 - October 2017

FIS Global,

Floor 1, Tricorn House, 51/53 Hagley Road, Birmingham B16 8TU.

#### Responsibilities include:

- Provide 24x7 alert monitoring of various financial applications on Windows, Linux, AIX, Networks and IBM AS400 platforms using Smart Cloud, Solarwinds, and bespoke in house monitoring tools.
- Monitoring of batch processing using Control-M including first fix resolution, escalation and incident management in accordance with SLAs.
- Management of incidents and changes using Service Now.

#### **Systems Operator**

May 2015 - July 2016

APSU,

5 Eastwood Business Village, Harry Weston Road, Coventry, CV3 2UB.

#### Responsibilities include:

- Provide 24x7 alert monitoring for a variety of customers on Windows, Linux, Networks and IBM AS400 platforms using Zenoss and What's Up Gold monitoring tools, working 12 hour shifts, including escalation and incident management in accordance with SLAs.
- > Performing backups / restores and tape management on Windows platforms using Backup Exec 2012 via Quantum tape libraries.
- Performing manual backups, IPLs, batch processing and ensuring high availability replication via Mimix, OMS and ODS on AS400 platform.
- > Providing out of hours helpdesk cover and first line support for different customers, including logging incidents on a variety of helpdesk systems including Service Now and Remedy.

## **Operations Analyst**

June 2014 - May 2015

The Coventry Building Society, High Street, Coventry, CV1 5QN.

## Responsibilities include:

- Provide Operational support including monitoring / setup of batch processing, backups, restores, incident management and resolution.
- Change management and release of code upgrades through system test to production systems on web and application Windows servers, Solaris servers and Oracle databases.
- Application of data fixes to production systems.

## NTT Data (Formerly Keane Canada),

300 – 2000 Barrington Street, Halifax, Nova Scotia, B3J 3K1. Canada.

#### Responsibilities include:

- Provide L2 /L3 application support, troubleshooting and issue resolution for Morgan Stanley's reporting infrastructure products on Linux and Windows platforms.
- Communicate critical system availability to business units for outages and scheduled maintenance and provide timely updates as required.
- Provide outage management, ensuring all relevant teams are engaged to facilitate a speedy resolution to critical issues.
- Ensure documentation is current, creating and updating FAQs and maintenance runbooks as required.

#### Various Short-Term Positions

March 2009 - August 2010

I moved from the UK to Canada in June 2010 and took various short-term jobs whilst arranging the relocation and settling in a new country.

## Systems Operator

January 2003 - February 2009

The Nottingham Building Society,

Upper Parliament Street, Nottingham. NG1 2BX

## Responsibilities include:

- Provide routine operational support of the infrastructure, including systems availability, security, performance and capacity monitoring, working 12.5 hour shifts providing 24 x 7 cover
- Carry out production work scheduling, batch processing and management
- Backup, restore and archive management
- > Provide input to disaster recovery plans and undertake disaster recovery testing
- Hardware monitoring/support, including call out and management of 3rd party maintenance providers
- > Contribute to the development and maintenance of system support procedures
- > Contribute to change management plans and ensure compliance with change management procedures
- > Provide Service Desk cover outside of "normal" hours

## **Application Support Technician**

July 2002 - December 2002

#### Traderman Systems Ltd, Tamworth

Providing L2 /L3 technical support to users of Traderman bespoke logistics, accounts and payroll software on SCO-Unix and AIX platforms.

#### Unix Support Technician

April 1999 - December 2000

#### The Post Office, Chesterfield

Providing L2 technical support for hardware, operating system and application issues on approximately 500 Unix servers.

# Computer Operator

January 1999 - March 1999

### The Post Office, Chesterfield

Providing alert monitoring of communications networks on Frame Relay Network Monitor, X25 Network Monitor and Cisco Router Network Monitor. Also, alert monitoring/initial investigation and fault diagnosis/rectification of Unix and NT Servers.

Computer Operations Shift Leader
From Junior to Senior Computer Operator

June 1998 – January 1999 May 1995 – June 1998

British Midland Airways, Castle Donington, Derby

- Ensuring system availability and completion of scheduled work, including system shutdown, IPL, back-ups, batch processing and bulk printing and splitting of reports on IBM Mainframe IBM ES9000 running VMESA, VSE/ESA, CICS, VTAM, TPX, CMS, EPIC, Oracle, Data General Unix Servers running DG-UX, IBM RS6000 running AIX and PC Network Servers running Novell, Windows 3.1 / 95 / NT 4, MSDOS, MS Office, Arcserve, MS Mail, Novell, Datastore.
- Managed a shift of 3 people, including conducting training and performance reviews.

## **Professional Development**

#### Courses completed:

- ➤ SQL Boot Camp
- iSeries Operations
- > Introduction to ITIL
- Windows 2003 Server Administration
- > Solaris 10 System Administration
- > HP-UX System and Network Administration
- HP-UX Logical Volume Manager and Mirror Disk / UX
- > SAP Basis Introduction and overview
- > IBM AIX System Administration Part 1
- Lotus Notes
- > IBM VM, VSE, CICS, VTAM, POWER
- > IBM Hardware Management Console
- > Introduction to Unix
- Microsoft Outlook, Word, Excel

## **Education**

BSc (Honours) First Class in Environment Undergraduate Diploma in Pollution Control RSA 1 Typewriting, BTEC Diploma in Engineering 8 GCE O-Levels including Mathematics and English

# **IT Competencies**

## **Operating Systems include:**

Windows – XP/ NT/ Server 2003 / Server 2008 / 7 /10 Unix – AIX/ Solaris/ HPUX/ SCO-Unix/ NCR, Linux - RHEL AS400 IBM VM/VSE

#### **Applications include:**

Oracle 11g / 12c Apex SQL Server Management Studio SQL\*Plus SQL Developer

Microsoft Exchange Microsoft Active Directory Microsoft Office / Office365 Sharepoint

Putty / ptman Winscp Cygwin

Autosys Control-M Cosbatch Maestro

Service Now Remedy Royal Blue Support Magic Service Desk

Smart Cloud Check\_MK Solarwinds Zenoss What's Up Gold ITOpenview BMC Patrol

Backup Exec Symantec Netbackup Omniback Arcserve

Mimix, OMS, ODS CICS, VTAM, POWER